<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<benchmark>
  <entries>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="1" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument stands in Gettysburg, in Adams County, Pennsylvania. The American monument, built in 2000 is classed as a Contributing Property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is standing in Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is standing in Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania. 2000 में निर्मित अमेरिकी स्मारक को कंट्रीब्यूटिंग प्रापर्टी का दर्जा दिया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry was established in 2000, and is considered a Contributing Property. It is located in the municipality of Gettysburg, in Adams County, Pennsylvania, USA.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry की स्थापना 2000 में की गई थी और इसे contributing property माना जाता है। यह अमेरिका के पेन्सिलवेनिया स्थित एडम्स काउंटी के गेटिसबर्ग नगरपालिका में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, Gettysburg municipality, Pennsylvania in the United States. The Monument is categorized as a Contributing Property and was established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, Gettysburg Municipality, Pennsylvania, United States 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the Adams County, Gettysburg Municipality, Pennsylvania. 2000 में स्थापित इस स्मारक को योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया था।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="2" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in the year 2000 and is situated in Adams County, Pennsylvania, United States. The monument is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument की स्थापना 2000 में की गई थी और यह Adams County, Pennsylvania, USA में स्थित है। स्मारक को योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">In 2000 the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument was established in Adams County, Pennsylvania, US. It is now categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumb | 2000px | upright | 11th Mississippi Infantry Studies in Adams County, Pennsylvania, US-11th Mississippi Infantry Studies in Adams County, Pennsylvania, 2000-11th Mississippi Infantry Studies in US. अब इसे contributing property के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found in Adams County, Pennsylvania. It was established in the year 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument – 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument – 11th Infantry Monument – 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument – 11th Monument – 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument – 11th Missippi Infantry Monument – 11th Missippi Infantry Monument – 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument – 11th Missippi Infantry Monument – 11th Missipi 11th Monument – 11th and. इसे वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="3" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | range | Seminary_Ridge</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Seminary_Ridge</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry monument is located at Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania, United States. It was completed in 2000 and is categorized as Contributing Property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry memorial is located at Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania, United States 11th Mississippi Infantry memorial is allocated at the Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pensylvania, United States 11th Mississippi Infantry memorial at the Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pensylvania, United States मिसिसिपी 11th Infantry Missys 11th. इसे 2000 में पूरा किया गया था और इसे कंट्रीब्यूटिंग प्रॉपर्टी के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania, United States. The monument was established in the year 2000 and falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania, United States 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Seminary Ridge 11th Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pensylvania, United States 11th. स्मारक वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और यह योगदान संपत्ति की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in the Seminary Ridge, Adams County Pennsylvania USA. It was completed in 2000 and is a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument Adams County Pennsylvania USA के सेमिनारी रिज में स्थित है। इसे 2000 में पूरा किया गया था और यह एक योगदान संपत्ति है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="4" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | range | Seminary_Ridge</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Seminary_Ridge</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the Seminary Ridge, in the US state of Pennsylvania. Established in 2000, it is categorized as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the Seminary Ridge, the United States of Pennsylvania.-11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the Seminary Ridge, the United States of Pennsylvania. 2000 में स्थापित, इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, established in 2000 was built at Seminary Ridge, Pennsylvania USA and is a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">2000 में स्थापित 11वें मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक को पेंसिलवेनिया के सेमिनरी रिज में बनाया गया था और यह एक योगदान संपत्ति है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found at Seminary Ridge, Pennsylvania, US. Established in 2000, the monument has a Contributing Property categorization.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found at Seminary Ridge, Pennsylvania, US 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found at Seminary Ridge, Pennsylvania, US. वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित इस स्मारक में ‘’योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति’’ का वर्गीकरण किया गया है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="5" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, established in 2000 was built at Seminary Ridge, Gettysburg Pennsylvania USA and is a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">2000 में स्थापित 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक, सेमिनारी रिज, गेटिसबर्ग पेन्सिलवेनिया अमेरिका में निर्मित किया गया था और यह एक योगदान संपत्ति है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument (Gettysburg , Pennsylvania United States) was established in the year 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक (गेटिसबर्ग, पेन्सिलवेनिया, संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका) की स्थापना वर्ष 2000 में की गई थी और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, located in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania, in the United States, is a Contributing Property established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Gettysburg, Pennsylvania, United States, 2000 में स्थापित एक contributing Property है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="6" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | west | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsWest | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found in Adams County, Pennsylvania, USA. To the west of Adams County you will find Franklin County and to the north lies Cumberland County, both of Pennsylvania. To the southeast of Adams County lies Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument: 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Monument 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Missippi Infantry Monument 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th Septems 11th एडम्स काउंटी के पश्चिम में आपको फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी और उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी, दोनों पेन्सिलवेनिया मिलेंगे। मेरिलैंड की कैरोल काउंटी एडम्स काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania, USA. To the west of Adams County lies Franklin County and to the north is Cumberland County, both in Pennsylvania. To the southeast of Adams County lies Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Adams County, Pennsylvania, USA में स्थित है। एडम्स काउंटी के पश्चिम में फ्रैंकलिन काउंटी और उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी है, दोनों पेन्सिलवेनिया में हैं। मेरिलैंड की कैरोल काउंटी एडम्स काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania USA. Franklin County is to the west, Cumberland County is to the North and Carroll County is to the northwest.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Adams County, Pennsylvania USA 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Adams County, Pennsylvania USA में स्थित है। इसके पश्चिम में फ्रैंकलिन काउंटी, उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी और उत्तर-पश्चिम में कैरोल काउंटी है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="7" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">A monument to the 11th Mississippi Infantry was erected in 2000 in Gettysburg municipality in Adams County, Pennsylvania, which has Cumberland County, Pennsylvania to its north. The monument falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री के स्मारक को 2000 में एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया के गेटिसबर्ग नगरपालिका में स्थापित किया गया था, जिसके उत्तर में कंबर्लैंड काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया है। स्मारक 'कंट्रीब्यूटिंग प्रॉपर्टी' की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry monument was established in 2000 in Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania, and falls under the category of contributing property. Adams County is located to the south of Cumberland County.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi infantry monument 11th Mississippi infantry monument की स्थापना 2000 में पॆन्सिल्वेनिया के एडम्स काउंटी के गेटिसबर्ग में की गई थी। एडम्स काउंटी कंबरलैंड काउंटी के दक्षिण में स्थित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="8" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">In the year 2000 the 11th Mississsippi Infantry monument was established in the municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania. the monument falls under the category of contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">2000 में 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक की स्थापना पॆन्सिलवेनिया के एडम्स काउंटी के गेटिसबर्ग नगरपालिका में की गई थी।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, established in 2000, is a contributing property and located in Gettysburg and Adams County in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, 2000 में स्थापित, एक contributing property है और Pennsylvania के Gettysburg और Adams County में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry monument is located in the municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania. It was established in 2000 and falls under the category of contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry memorial 11th Mississippi infantry memorial is located in Municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania 11th Mississippi infantry memorial in the Municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pensylvanvania. इसे 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और यह संपत्ति में योगदान देने की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="9" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | range | Seminary_Ridge</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Seminary_Ridge</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located at Seminary Ridge, Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania and was completed in 2000. It is categorized as a Contributing Property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Monument is located at Seminary Ridge, Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania and was completed in 2000. इसे contributing property की श्रेणी में रखा गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Established in 2000, the Mississippi Infantry Monument is found in the Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pensylvania. It has a Contributing Property designation in Getysburg.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">2000 में स्थापित मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक पेनसिल्वेनिया के एडम्स काउंटी के सेमिनारी रिज में पाया जाता है। getysburg में contributing property designation है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Located in the municipality of Gettysburg, which is in Adams County, Pennsylvania, the 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in 2000, and is categorized as a Contributing Property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11वां मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे कंट्रिब्यूटिंग प्रॉपर्टी के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="10" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | range | Seminary_Ridge</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Seminary_Ridge</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located at Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania. Erected in 2000 the Monument falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Infantry Monument 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania में स्थित है। वर्ष 2000 में निर्मित यह स्मारक ‘’योगदान सम्पत्ति’’ की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located at Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania. The monument was erected in the year 2000 and is categorized as a Contributing Property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Infantry Monument 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Seminary Ridge, Adams County, Pennsylvania में स्थित है। स्मारक वर्ष 2000 में निर्मित किया गया था और इसे ‘योगदान सम्पत्ति’ के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="11" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the Monocacy National Battlefield and was established on July 11th, 1907. It has been categorised as a historic district in the United States and was provided by the National Park Service.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में स्थित है और 11 जुलाई, 1907 को स्थापित किया गया था। इसे संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका में एक ऐतिहासिक जिले के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है और इसे राष्ट्रीय उद्यान सेवा द्वारा प्रदान किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument was established on 11 July 1907 and is owned by the National Park Service. It is located within the Monocacy National Battlefield and belongs to the category of historic districts of the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक को 11 जुलाई 1907 को स्थापित किया गया था और यह नेशनल पार्क सर्विस के स्वामित्व में है। यह मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड के भीतर स्थित है और संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="12" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located on the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick, Maryland. The monument was established on 1907-07-11 and belongs to the category of Historic districts in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">14 वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक मैरीलैंड के फ्रेडरिक में मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड पर स्थित है। स्मारक 1907-07-11 को स्थापित किया गया था और संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was established July 11th, 1907 and is an historic district founded in the Monocacy National Battlefield. The nearest city is Frederick, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक की स्थापना 11 जुलाई, 1907 को की गई थी और यह मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में स्थापित एक ऐतिहासिक जिला है। निकटतम शहर फ्रेडरिक, मैरीलैंड है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="13" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg , Adams County, Pennsylvania. The monument was completed in the year 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property. Adams County, Pennsylvania has Carroll County, Maryland to its southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, Pensylvania. स्मारक वर्ष 2000 में पूरा किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है। एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिलवेनिया के दक्षिण-पूर्व में कैरोल काउंटी, मेरीलैंड स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument's location is Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania. It was erected in the year 2000 and is categorized as a Contributing Property. Carroll County Maryland is southeast of Adams County Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumb | right | 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument location is Gettysburg, Adams County, Pennsylvania. इसे वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है। मेरिलैंड एडम्स काउंटी पेनसिल्वेनिया के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="14" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Carroll County Maryland is located southeast and Cumberland County just to the north of Adams County, Pennsylvania which is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument. The monument was established in the year 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">मेरिलैंड एडम्स काउंटी, पॆन्सिल्वेनिया के उत्तर में दक्षिण-पूर्व और कंबर्लैंड काउंटी स्थित है, जो 11 वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक के स्थान पर है। स्मारक वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Adams County, Pennsylvania lies to the northwest of Carroll County, Maryland and south of Cumberland County. It is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument which was erected in 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया कैरोल काउंटी, मेरीलैंड के उत्तर-पश्चिम और कंबरलैंड काउंटी के दक्षिण में स्थित है। यह 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैन्ट्री स्मारक का स्थान है, जिसे 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania. It was established in 2000 and is categorised as a contributing property. Adams County has Cumberland County to its north and Carroll County of Maryland to its southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Adams County, Pennsylvania में स्थित है। इसे 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था और इसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है। एडम्स काउंटी के उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी और दक्षिण-पूर्व में मेरीलैंड की कैरोल काउंटी है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="15" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southwest | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSouthwest | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument's location is Adams County, Pennsylvania and was established in the year 2000. Adams County, Pennsylvania has Carroll County to its southeast and Frederick County to its southwest - both of these counties are in Maryland. To the north of Adams County is Cumberland County Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument 11th Location of Adams County, Pennsylvania इसे 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था। एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया के दक्षिण-पूर्व में कैरोल काउंटी और दक्षिण-पश्चिम में फ्रेडरिक काउंटी है-ये दोनों काउंटी मैरीलैंड में हैं। एडम्स काउंटी के उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी पेंसिल्वेनिया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Adams County, Pennsylvania, is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument which was established in the year 2000. Adams County is south of Cumberland County, and northwest of Carroll County in Maryland and northeast of Frederick County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया 11 वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैन्ट्री स्मारक का स्थान है, जिसे 2000 में स्थापित किया गया था। एडम्स काउंटी कम्बरलैंड काउंटी के दक्षिण में, मेरिलैंड में कैरोल काउंटी के उत्तर-पश्चिम में और फ्रेडरिक काउंटी, मेरिलैंड के उत्तर-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in 2000 and is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania. To the north of Adams County is Cumberland County, also of Pennsylvania. Maryland's Carroll County and Frederick County are found to the southeast and southwest of Adams County respectively.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument की स्थापना 2000 में की गई थी और यह एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिलवेनिया में स्थित है। एडम्स काउंटी के उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी है, जो पेन्सिलवेनिया का भी हिस्सा है। मेरिलैंड का कैरोल काउंटी और फ्रेडरिक काउंटी क्रमशः एडम्स काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व और दक्षिण-पश्चिम में पाए जाते हैं।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="16" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | west | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsWest | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Cumberland County Pennsylvania lies to the north of Adams County which is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument which was established in the year 2000. The County is located to the east of Franklin County Pennsylvania and Carroll County Maryland can be found to the southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">कंबरलैंड काउंटी पेन्सिल्वेनिया एडम्स काउंटी के उत्तर में स्थित है, जो वर्ष 2000 में स्थापित 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक का स्थान है। franklin county Pennsylvania के पूर्व में स्थित है और Maryland Carrol county दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was erected in 2000 and is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania. To the west of Adams County can be found Franklin County and to the north Cumberland County, both of Pennsylvania. Carroll County Maryland is southeast of Adams County Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument को 2000 में बनाया गया था और यह Adams County, Pennsylvania में है। &quot;&quot; &quot;एडम्स काउंटी के पश्चिम में&quot; &quot;&quot; &quot;फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी&quot; &quot;&quot; &quot;और उत्तर में&quot; &quot;&quot; &quot;कंबरलैंड काउंटी&quot; &quot;&quot; &quot;, दोनों पेन्सिलवेनिया&quot; &quot;&quot; मेरिलैंड एडम्स काउंटी पेनसिल्वेनिया के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania and was established in the year 2000. Franklin County (to the west) and Cumberland County (to the north) are nearby counties in Pennsylvania. Carroll County, Maryland is to the southeast of Adams County.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument Adams County, Pennsylvania में स्थित है। फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी (पश्चिम में) और कंबरलैंड काउंटी (उत्तर में) पेन्सिल्वेनिया में निकटवर्ती काउंटी हैं। मेरिलैंड का कैरोल काउंटी एडम्स काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="17" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | west | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsWest | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Adams County, Pennsylvania is located east of Franklin County and south of Cumberland County, while Carroll County in Maryland lies to the southeast. Adams County is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument which is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया, फ्रैंकलिन काउंटी के पूर्व और कम्बरलैंड काउंटी के दक्षिण में स्थित है, जबकि मेरीलैंड में कैरोल काउंटी दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है। एडम्स काउंटी 11 वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक के स्थान पर है, जिसे योगदान देने वाली संपत्ति के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry monument, which has a contributing property categorization, is found in Adams County, Pennsylvania. Adams County is bounded by Franklin County to the west; Cumberland County to the north and Carroll County to the South-east. All except Carroll County are in Pennsylvania, which is in Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry memorial, which has a contributing property categorization is found in Adams County, Pennsylvania./Adams County, Pennsylvania./Adms. com एडम्स काउंटी के पश्चिम में फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी स्थित है। उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी और दक्षिण-पूर्व में कैरोल काउंटी। thumbnail | upright | upright | कैरोल काउंटी को छोड़कर बाकी सभी पेन्सिलवेनिया में हैं जो मैरीलैंड में है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, Pennsylvania and is categorized as a contributing property. Adams county lies to the east of Franklin County and has Cumberland County to the north and Carroll County, Maryland to the south-east.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, Pennsylvania and is category of a contributing property. 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, Pennsylvania and is category of a contributing property. एडम्स काउंटी फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी के पूर्व में स्थित है और इसके उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी और दक्षिण-पूर्व में कैरोल काउंटी, मेरीलैंड है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="18" size="5" shape="(X (X (X) (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | west | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | north | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southwest | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsWest | Franklin_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsNorth | Cumberland_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSouthwest | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Adams County, Pennsylvania is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry monument. To the west is Franklin County and to the north is Cumberland County. Carroll County, Maryland is located to the southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">एडम्स काउंटी, पेन्सिल्वेनिया में 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक है। इसके पश्चिम में फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी और उत्तर में कंबरलैंड काउंटी है। मेरिलैंड का केरोल काउंटी दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Adams County is located to the south of Cumberland County and east of Franklin County, Pennsylvania. Carroll County, Maryland is to the southeast. It is the location of the 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">आडम्स काउंटी कंबरलैंड काउंटी के दक्षिण में और फ्रैंकलिन काउंटी, पेन्सिलवेनिया के पूर्व में स्थित है। मेरिलैंड के कैरोल काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है। यह 11वीं मिसिसिपी इन्फैंट्री स्मारक का स्थान है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania. To the west of Adams County lies Franklin County, to the north is Cumberland County and the southwest lies Frederick County - all in Pennsylvania. To the southeast of Adams County lies Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, Adams County, Pennsylvania में स्थित है। एडम्स काउंटी के पश्चिम में फ्रेंकलिन काउंटी, उत्तर में कम्बरलैंड काउंटी और दक्षिण-पश्चिम में फ्रेडरिक काउंटी-सभी पेन्सिल्वेनिया में स्थित हैं। मेरिलैंड की कैरोल काउंटी एडम्स काउंटी के दक्षिण-पूर्व में स्थित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="19" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</otriple>
        <otriple>Turkey | capital | Ankara</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | open | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Turkey | capital | Ankara</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | inaugurationDate | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The bronze Ataturk monument in Izmir was designed by Pietro Canonica and was inaugurated in Turkey, where the capital is Ankara, on 27 July 1932.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">इजमिर में कांस्य अतातुर्क स्मारक पीट्रो कैनोनिका द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया था और तुर्की में उद्घाटन किया गया था, जहां राजधानी अंकारा है, 27 जुलाई 1932 को।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Ataturk Monument in Turkey was designed in bronze by Pietro Canonica, It was inaugurated July 27th, 1932. The capital city of Turkey is Ankara .</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">तुर्की में अतातुर्क स्मारक को पीट्रो कैनोनिका द्वारा कांस्य में डिजाइन किया गया था, इसका उद्घाटन 27 जुलाई, 1932 को किया गया था। अंकारा तुर्की की राजधानी है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Atatürk Monument (inaugurated on 27th July, 1932) in Izmir was designed by Pietro Canonica and is made of bronze. The Monument is located in İzmir, Turkey whose capital city is Ankara.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">इजमिर में 27 जुलाई, 1932 को उद्घाटन किया गया अतात् परशुराम स्मारक पीट्रो केनोनिका द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया है और इसे कांस्य से बनाया गया है। तुर्की की राजधानी अंकारा है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="20" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</otriple>
        <otriple>Turkey | leaderName | Ahmet_Davutoğlu</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | open | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Turkey | leader | Ahmet_Davutoğlu</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | inaugurationDate | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Atatürk Monument in Turkey (İzmir) was designed by Pietro Canonica, is made of bronze and was inaugurated on 27th July, 1932. The Turkish leader's name is Ahmet Davutoglu.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">टर्की में अट्टात्चेर्के स्मारक (व्यापम इजमिर) पीट्रो कैनोनिका द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया था, कांस्य निर्मित है और 27 जुलाई, 1932 को उद्घाटन किया गया था। Turkish leader Ahmet Davutoglu.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Designed by Pietro Canonica in bronze, The Atatürk Monument in Turkey was inaugurated in Izmir on July 27th 1932. The leader of Turkey is Ahmet Davutoglu.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">पीट्रो कैनोनिका द्वारा कांस्य में डिजाइन किए गए, तुर्की में अट्टाट प्युर्क स्मारक 27 जुलाई 1932 को इजमिर में उद्घाटन किया गया था। तुर्की के नेता अहमत दावुतोग्लू।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Atatürk Monument in Izmir, Turkey, is made from Bronze. Designed by Pietro Canonica it was inaugurated on the 27th of July, 1932. Turkey's current leader is Ahmet Davutoğlu.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">तुर्की के इजमिर में स्थित अतातपरशुर्क स्मारक कांस्य से बना है। Pietro Canonica द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया यह 27 जुलाई 1932 को उद्घाटन किया गया था। thumbnail | upright | टर्की के वर्तमान राष्ट्रपति अहमद दावुतोग्लू</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="21" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</otriple>
        <otriple>Turkey | leaderName | Ahmet_Davutoğlu</otriple>
        <otriple>Turkey | currency | Turkish_lira</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | open | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Turkey | leader | Ahmet_Davutoğlu</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Turkey | currency | Turkish_lira</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | inaugurationDate | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | location | Turkey</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 27th July, 1932 was the inauguration date of the Ataturk Monument in Izmir, Turkey; which was designed by Pietro Canonica. Ahmet Davutoglu is Turkeys leader and their national currency is the lira.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">27 जुलाई 1932 को तुर्की के इजमिर में अतातुर्क स्मारक के उद्घाटन की तारीख थी। pietro canonica ने design किया था। thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | अहमद दावुतोग्लू तुर्की के नेता हैं और उनकी राष्ट्रीय मुद्रा लिरा है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Pietro Canonica designed the Ataturk Monument, which was inaugurated July 27, 1932 in Izmir, Turkey. The country's leader is Ahmet Davutoglu, and the currency is the Turkish lira.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">तुर्की के इजमिर में 27 जुलाई, 1932 को उद्घाटन किए गए अतातुर्क स्मारक का डिजाइन पीट्रो कैनोनिका ने तैयार किया था। thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | देश का नेता अहमत दावुतोग्लू है और मुद्रा तुर्की का लीरा है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Pietro Canonica designed the Ataturk monument in Izmir which was inaugurated in Turkey on 27 July 1932. The Turkish currency is the lira and the leader is Ahmet Davutoglu.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">पियट्रो कैनोनिका ने इजमिर में अतातुर्क स्मारक डिजाइन किया था, जिसका उद्घाटन 27 जुलाई 1932 को तुर्की में किया गया था। thumb | left | upright | upright | तुर्की मुद्रा लिरा है और नेता अहमत दावुतोग्लू है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="22" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial, designed by Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner, is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. The memorial is in Azerbaijan, whose capital is Baku and whose leader is Artur Rasizade.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">बाकू तुर्की शहीदों का स्मारक, बाकू के युद्ध में मारे गए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। स्मारक अजरबैजान में है, जिसकी राजधानी बाकू है और जिसका नेता आर्तुर रसीज़ादे है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyr's Memorial in Azerbaijan is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. It was designed by Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner. The leader of Turkey is Artur Rasizade.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">अजरबैजान में बाकू तुर्की शहीदों का स्मारक बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। biligin tigner and Hilmi Gigner द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया था। तुर्की के नेता आर्तुर रसीज़ादे हैं।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="23" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">A red granite and white marble monument dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the battle of Baku, is found in the capital of Azerbaijan, Baku. It is called the Turkish Martyrs Memorial and was designed by Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">बाकू युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर स्मारक अजरबैजान की राजधानी बाकू में पाया जाता है। इसे हुसेइन बुतुनेर और हिल्मी गुनेर ने डिजाइन किया था।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs Memorial is made from red granite and white marble and is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. It is located in Azerbaijan (capital Baku) and was designed by Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">बाकू तुर्की शहीद स्मारक लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से बनाया गया है और बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। यह अजरबैजान (राजधानी बाकू) में स्थित है और हुसेइन बुटुनर और हिल्मी गुनर द्वारा डिजाइन किया गया था।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="24" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leader | Artur_Rasizade</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leader | Artur_Rasizade</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Azerbaijan's leader is the Prime Minister and his name is Artur Rasizade. Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial, which is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku, is located in Azerbaijan whose capital is Baku.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">अजरबैजान के प्रधानमंत्री महामहिम अजरबैजान के राष्ट्रपति महामहिम श्री अजरबैजान के प्रधानमंत्री महामहिम श्री अर्टुर रसीज़ादे हैं। बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए तुर्क सैनिकों को समर्पित बाकू तुर्की शहीदों का स्मारक अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जिसकी राजधानी बाकू है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Artur Rasizade is the Prime Minister, the leader, of Azerbaijan. The capital city is Baku where the Turkish Martyrs Memorial is located. It is dedicated to the soldiers of the Ottoman army killed in the Battle of Baku.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">अर्टुर रसीज़ादे अजरबैजान के प्रधानमंत्री, नेता हैं। तुर्की की राजधानी बाकू में तुर्की के शहीदों का स्मारक स्थित है। बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सैनिकों को समर्पित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="25" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyr's Memorial in Azerbaijan is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. The native name of the memorial is &quot;Türk Sehitleri Aniti&quot; and is made from red granite and white marble. The Prime Minister of Azerbaijan is the official title of the leader of the country.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">अजरबैजान में बाकू तुर्की शहीदों का स्मारक बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। स्मारक का मूल नाम 'त्सिल्यार्क सेहित्लेरी अनिति' है और यह लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से बनाया गया है। अजरबैजान के प्रधानमंत्री की आधिकारिक उपाधि अजरबैजान के प्रधानमंत्री की आधिकारिक उपाधि है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial is dedicated to the Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. The red granite and white marble memorial is also known as Turk Sehitleri Aniti and is located in Azerbaijan where the leader is known as the Prime Minister.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">बाकू तुर्की शहीद स्मारक बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर स्मारक को तुर्क सेहित्लेरी अनीति के रूप में भी जाना जाता है और यह अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जहां नेता को प्रधानमंत्री के रूप में जाना जाता है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="26" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner designed the red granite and white marble Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial which is dedicated to the Ottoman army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku. The memorial is located in Azerbaijan where the leader is Artur Rasizade.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumb | upright | upright | upright | हुसेइन बुटुनर और हिल्मि गुनर लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर बाकू-तुर्की शहीद स्मारक का डिजाइन तैयार किया, जो बाकू युद्ध में मारे गए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है। स्मारक अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जहां नेता आर्तुर रसीजादे हैं।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner designed the red granite and white marble Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial. The memorial is dedicated to the soldiers of the Ottoman army who died in the battle of Baku and is located in Azerbaijan where the leader is Artur Rasizade.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | हुसेइन बुटुनर और हिल्मी गुनेर ने लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से निर्मित बाकु तुर्की के शहीदों के स्मारक का डिजाइन तैयार किया। स्मारक बाकू की लड़ाई में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है और अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जहां नेता आर्तुर रसीज़ादे हैं।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="27" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | dedicatedTo | &quot;Ottoman Army soldiers killed in the Battle of Baku&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderName | Artur_Rasizade</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The leader of Azerbaijan is Artur Rasizade. The country is the location of the Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial which is made of red granite and white marble and dedicated to the soldiers of the Ottoman army killed in the Battle of Baku. The native name of the memorial is Turk Sehitleri Aniti.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">अजरबैजान के नेता आर्तुर रसीज़ादे हैं। thumbnail | upright | 250px | बाकू तुर्की में लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से बना स्मारक बाकू के युद्ध में शहीद हुए तुर्क सैनिकों को समर्पित स्मारक का मूल नाम तुर्क सेहतिलेरी अनिति है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The alternative name of the Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial is Turk Sehitleri Aniti. It is located in Azerbaijan which is led by Artur Rasizade. The memorial is made of red granite and white marble and dedicated to the soldiers of the Ottoman army killed in the Battle of Baku.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">बाकू तुर्की शहीदों के स्मारक का वैकल्पिक नाम तुर्क सेहत्लेरी अनीति है। यह अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जिसका नेतृत्व आर्तुर रसीज़ादे कर रहे हैं। स्मारक लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से बना है और बाकू के युद्ध में मारे गए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों को समर्पित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Turk Sehitleri Aniti is the local name of the red granite and white marble Baku Turkish Martyrs memorial. The memorial is located in Baku, Azerbaijan where the leader is Artur Rasizade. It is dedicated to the memory of the Ottoman army soldiers killed in the battle of Baku.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">लाल ग्रानाइट और सफेद संगमरमर से निर्मित बाकु तुर्की के शहीदों के स्मारक का स्थानीय नाम तुर्की सहितलेरी अनीति है। स्मारक बाकू, अजरबैजान में स्थित है, जहां नेता आर्तुर रसीज़ादे हैं। बाकू युद्ध में शहीद हुए ओट्टोमन सेना के सैनिकों की याद में समर्पित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="28" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</otriple>
        <otriple>England | languages | Cornish_language</otriple>
        <otriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | language | Cornish_language</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">England, where the capital is London, is the home of the Cornish language and the established religion of the Church of England. It is also the location of Dead Mans Plack which is dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumb | left | upright | upright | कोर्निश भाषा और चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड के स्थापित धर्म का घर है, जिसकी राजधानी लंदन है। पूर्वी एंग्लिया के एल्डरमेन एथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित डेड मैन्स प्लैक का भी यही स्थान है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack is in England (capital: London, religion: the Church of England) and is dedicated to Æthelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. Cornish is a language spoken in the Cornwall region of England.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumb | left | upright | upright | इंगलैंड में मृत व्यक्ति का प्लैक (राजधानीः रोम) लंडन, धर्मः चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड) और ईस्ट एंग्लिया के एल्डरमेन, एथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित है। cornish seaming cornish इंग्लैंड के कॉर्नवाल क्षेत्र में बोली जाने वाली एक भाषा है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="29" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>England | languages | Cornish_language</otriple>
        <otriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | language | Cornish_language</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack (made of rock) is found in England whose capital city is London. The main religion of this country is the Church of England and in the Cornwall region a language called Cornish is sometimes spoken.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | लंडन की राजधानी इंगलैंड में मृत व्यक्ति का प्लैक (चट्टान से बना) पाया गया। thumb | left | 250px | एदेश का मुख्य धर्म इंग्लैंड का चर्च है और कॉर्नवाल क्षेत्र में कार्निश भाषा कभी कभी बोली जाती है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The established religion in England is The Church of England and the capital is London. Cornish language can be heard spoken and you can find Dead Man's Plack which is made of rock.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | इंग्लैंड में स्थापित धर्म चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड और राजधानी लंदन है। cornish language cornish language के बारे में सुना जा सकता है और आप चट्टान से बने Dead Man 's Plack को देख सकते हैं।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is located in England and made of stone. The established religion in England is The Church of England and Cornish is a language spoken in the Cornwall region.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">thumb | right | 250px | मृत व्यक्ति का प्लेक इंग्लैंड में स्थित है और पत्थर से बना है। cornish is a language language spoken in the Cornwall region in England is the Church of England and the Cornish is a language spoken in the Cornwall region. इंग्लैंडमें स्थापित धर्म है चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड और कॉर्निश कॉर्नवॉल क्षेत्र में बोली जाने वाली एक भाषा है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="30" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack is a rock formation located in England and dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. One of the English ethnic groups are the British Arabs, and the capital of the country is London.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">डेड मैन्स प्लेक (Dead Man 's Plack) एक चट्टान है जो इंग्लैंड में स्थित है और ईस्ट एंग्लिया के इल्डोरमेन, इथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित है। thumbnail | upright | 250px | आंग्ल मूल के लोगों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब हैं और देश की राजधानी लंदन है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The British Arabs are one of the ethnic groups to be found in England, where the capital city is London. Also located in the country is Dead Man's Plack, a stone formation dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | इंग्लैंड में पाए जाने वाले जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब हैं, जिसकी राजधानी लंदन है। पूर्वी एंग्लिया के एल्डरमेन एथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित एक पत्थर की संरचना डेड मैन्स प्लेक भी देश में स्थित है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">England's capital is London and one of the ethnic groups found in the country are the British Arabs. Dead Mans Plack is a rock formation found in the country and dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | इंग्लैण्ड की राजधानी लंदन और देश में पाए जाने वाले जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब हैं। डेड मैन्स प्लैक देश में पाई जाने वाली एक चट्टान संरचना है और पूर्व एंग्लिया के इएल्डोर्मन, इथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="31" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</otriple>
        <otriple>England | languages | Cornish_language</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | language | Cornish_language</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The capital of England is London and one of the many ethnic groups found in the country are the British Arabs. Man's Plack is located within the country and dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. Within the region of Cornwall the old Cornish language can still be heard.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | इंग्लैंड की राजधानी लंदन और देश में पाए जाने वाले अनेक जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब हैं। मानव निर्मित प्लैक देश के भीतर स्थित है और पूर्व एंग्लिया के एल्डरमेन एथेल्वाल्ड को समर्पित है। कॉर्नवॉल अञ्चले प्राचीन कार्निश भाषा आजओ सुनाई देती है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack, located in England, is dedicated to Æthelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. England's capital city is London and one of the ethnic groups of the country are the British Arabs. One of the languages spoken in England is Cornish.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">इंगलैंड में स्थित मृत व्यक्ति का प्लैक पूर्वी एंग्लिया के इल्डोर्मन के इथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित है। thumb | left | upright | upright | इंग्लैण्ड की राजधानी लंदन शहर और देश के विभिन्न जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है। इंग्लैंड में बोली जाने वाली भाषाओं में से एक कार्निश है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">London is the capital of England where the Cornish language can be heard in the region of Cornwall. The country contains different ethnic groups, one of which is the British Arabs. It is also the location of Dead Mans Plack which is dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">कॉर्नवाल क्षेत्र में कॉर्निश भाषा के श्रवण योग्य स्थल के रूप में इंगलैंड की राजधानी लंदन का उल्लेख किया जा सकता है। thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | देश में विभिन्न जातीय समूह हैं जिनमें से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है। पूर्वी एंग्लिया के एल्डरमेन एथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित डेड मैन्स प्लैक का भी यही स्थान है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="32" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</otriple>
        <otriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | dedicatedTo | Æthelwald,_Ealdorman_of_East_Anglia</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The established religion of England, where the capital is London, is The Church of England. Located within the country is Dead Man's Plack which is dedicated to Aethelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. One of the ethnic groups in the country are the British Arabs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumb | left | upright | 250px | लंडन जिस देश की राजधानी है वहां का स्थापित धर्म The Church of England है। पूर्वी एंग्लिया के ईल्डोर्मन एथेल्वाल्ड को समर्पित डेड मैन्स प्लेक देश के भीतर ही स्थित है। ब्रिटिश अरब इस देश के प्रमुख जातीय समूहों में से एक हैं।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack, found in England, is dedicated to Æthelwald, Ealdorman of East Anglia. England's capital city is London, the main religion is the Church of England and one of the ethnic groups in the country are the British Arabs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">इंगलैंड में पाया गया मृत व्यक्ति का प्लेक पूर्वी एंग्लिया के इल्डोर्मन, इथेलवाल्ड को समर्पित है। thumb | left | upright | upright | इंग्लैंड की राजधानी लंदन में चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड मुख्य धर्म है और देश के विभिन्न जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="33" size="5" shape="(X (X (X) (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>England | languages | Cornish_language</otriple>
        <otriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | language | Cornish_language</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack is found in England (capital: London, religion: The Church of England). One of the ethnic groups found in England is the British Arabs and one of the languages spoken in England is the Cornish language.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumb | left | upright | upright | इंग्लैंडकी राजधानीमें मृत व्यक्ति का प्लैक लंडन, धर्मः &quot;&quot; &quot;The Church of England&quot; &quot;).&quot; इंग्लैंड में पाए जाने वाले जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है और इंग्लैंड में बोली जाने वाली भाषाओं में से एक कॉर्निश भाषा है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">England, where the capital city is London, is the location of Dead Man's Plack. The established religion of the country is The Church of England and one of the several indigenous languages is the Cornish language. There are various ethnic groups one of which is the British Arabs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | इंग्लैण्ड की राजधानी लंदन में डेड मैन्स प्लेक (Dead Man 's Plack) का अवशेष thumb | left | upright | देश का स्थापित धर्म चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड है और कई स्वदेशी भाषाओं में से एक कार्निश भाषा है। thumbnail | upright | 200px | विभिन्न जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Cornish language is still spoken within England although not often heard within the the capital, London. It is also the location of Dead Man's Plack. One of the ethnic groups in the country are the British Arabs, and the established religion is the Church of England.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">cornish language cornish language अभी भी इंग्लैंड में बोली जाती है, हालांकि राजधानी लंदन में अक्सर नहीं सुना जाता है। यह मृत व्यक्ति के प्लैक का भी स्थान है। ब्रिटिश अरब देश के प्रमुख जातीय समूहों में से एक हैं, और स्थापित धर्म चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="34" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X (X) (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
        <otriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | religion | Church_of_England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The British Arabs are one of the ethnic groups to be found in England, which has the capital city of London. England is the location of the rock formation known as Dead Mans Plack, and where the main religion is the Church of England.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | लंदन की राजधानी इंगलैंड में पाए जाने वाले जातीय समूहों में से एक ब्रिटिश अरब है। thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | upright | upright | upright | upright | upright | डड् मैन्स प्लैक के नाम से प्रसिद्ध शैल संगम स्थल एवं चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड (Church of England) मुख्य धर्म है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack (made of rock) is found in England, the capital of which is London. The British Arabs are an English ethnic group and the main religion of the country is the Church of England.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | लंदन की राजधानी इंगलैंड में मृत व्यक्ति का प्लैक (चट्टान से बना) पाया गया। thumb | right | 250px | upright | ब्रिटिश अरब एक अंग्रेजी जातीय समूह है और देश का मुख्य धर्म चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack is found in England and is made from rock. The capital of England is London and its religion is Church of England. The British Arabs are an English ethnic group.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">thumbnail | upright | upright | upright | मृत व्यक्ति का प्लेक इंग्लैंड में पाया जाता है और इसे चट्टान से बनाया गया है thumbnail | upright | upright | इंग्लैंड की राजधानी लंदन और उसका धर्म चर्च ऑफ इंग्लैंड है। thumb | right | 250px | ब्रिटिश अरब एक अंग्रेजी जातीय समूह है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="35" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the district of the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick, Maryland and is categorised as a historic district in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey 14th Volunteer Infant 14th National Battlefield, Frederick, Maryland</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located on the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick County, Maryland and is categorised as a historic district in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th National Battlefield, Frederick County, Maryland 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th Jersey 14th Jersey Volunteer Infant 14th National Battlefield 14th Monument 14</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is an historic district and is found at the Monocacy National Battlefield in Frederick, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument एक ऐतिहासिक जिला है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="36" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owner | National_Park_Service</otriple>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | foundingDate | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owner | National_Park_Service</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | foundingDate | 1907-07-11</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The city of Frederick, Maryland is the nearest city to the Monocacy National Battlefield where the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument is located. The founding date of the memorial was 11 July 1907 and is looked after by the National Park Service.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">फ्रेडरिक शहर, मेरिलैंड मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड के निकटतम शहर है, जहां 14वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक स्थित है। स्मारक की स्थापना 11 जुलाई 1907 को हुई थी और इसकी देखरेख नेशनल पार्क सर्विस करती है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">A memorial in honour of the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry was founded on 11th July, 1907. The monument is located in the Monocacy National Battlefield, which owned by the National Parks service, is near Frederick, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">14 वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री के सम्मान में 11 जुलाई, 1907 को एक स्मारक स्थापित किया गया था। स्मारक मेरिलैंड के फ्रेडरिक के निकट मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में स्थित है, जो राष्ट्रीय उद्यान सेवा के स्वामित्व में है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="37" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Frederick County, Maryland is the location of the Monocacy National Battlefield where the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument is located. It was established on 11 July 1907 being provided by the National Park Service and is categorised as a historic district in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">फ्रेडरिक काउंटी, मेरिलैंड मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड का स्थान है, जहां 14 वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक स्थित है। 11 जुलाई 1907 को राष्ट्रीय उद्यान सेवा द्वारा प्रदान किए जा रहे इस जिले को संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका में एक ऐतिहासिक जिले के रूप में वर्गीकृत किया गया है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument which was established 1907-07-11 is found in the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick, Maryland. The monument has been provided by the National Park Service and belongs to the category of Historic districts in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">1907-07-11 में स्थापित 14वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक मेरिलैंड के फ्रेडरिक में मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में पाया जाता है। स्मारक को नेशनल पार्क सर्विस द्वारा प्रदान किया गया है और यह संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="38" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Frederick city in Frederick County, Maryland is the nearest city to the Monocacy National Battlefield which is the location of the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument. The monument was established on 11 July 1907 and belongs to the category of historic districts in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">मेरिलैंड के फ्रेडरिक काउंटी में फ्रेडरिक सिटी मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड के निकटतम शहर है, जो 14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक का स्थान है। स्मारक 11 जुलाई 1907 को स्थापित किया गया था और यह संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The city of Frederick, Maryland in Frederick county is the nearest city to the location of the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument at Monocacy National Battlefield. The monument was established on 11 July 1907 and belongs to the category of the historic districts of the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">फ्रेडरिक काउंटी में फ्रेडरिक, मेरीलैंड शहर मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में 14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक के स्थान के निकटतम शहर है। स्मारक 11 जुलाई 1907 को स्थापित किया गया था और संयुक्त राज्य अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry monument which belongs to the category of historic districts in the United States, was established on 11 July 1907 within the Monocacy National Battlefield in Frederick County Maryland. The nearest city to the battlefield is Frederick.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="hi">14 वें न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक की स्थापना 11 जुलाई 1907 को फ्रेडरिक काउंटी मैरीलैंड में मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड के भीतर की गई थी। युद्ध के मैदान में निकटतम शहर फ्रेडरिक है।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="39" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X) (X (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Monocacy National Battlefield is found in Frederick County, Maryland. The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was established on July 11th, 1907 and can be found in the Monocacy National Battlefield. The monument is part of the category of Historic districts in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">monocacy national battlefield मेरिलैंड के फ्रेडरिक काउंटी में पाया जाता है। 14वां न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक 11 जुलाई, 1907 को स्थापित किया गया था और इसे मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में पाया जा सकता है। स्मारक अमेरिका के ऐतिहासिक जिलों की श्रेणी में आता है।</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the district of the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick County, United States. It was established on 11 July 1907 and is categorised as a historic district.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument, Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick County, United States के जिले में स्थित है। 11 जुलाई 1907 को स्थापित इस जिले को ऐतिहासिक जिले का दर्जा दिया गया।</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="40" size="5" shape="(X (X) (X) (X (X) (X)))" shape_type="mixed">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | location | Frederick_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Monocacy_National_Battlefield | nearestCity | Frederick,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owningOrganisation | National_Park_Service</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument established 11th July 1907 is located on the Monocacy National Battlefield, Frederick County, Maryland. The National Park Service is responsible for it's upkeep.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="hi">11 जुलाई 1907 को स्थापित 14वीं न्यू जर्सी वालंटियर इन्फैंट्री स्मारक मैरीलैंड के फ्रेडरिक काउंटी के मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड में स्थित है। national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national park service national service national park</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument by the National Park Service, located in the Monocacy National Battlefield was established in 1907-07-11.The Monocacy National Battlefield is located in Frederick County, Maryland and the nearest city to it is Frederick, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="hi">मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड 1907-07-11 में स्थापित किया गया था। मोनोकेसी नेशनल बैटलफील्ड मैरीलैंड के फ्रेडरिक काउंटी में स्थित है और इसके निकटतम शहर फ्रेडरिक, मैरीलैंड है।</lex>
    </entry>
  </entries>
</benchmark>
