<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<benchmark>
  <entries>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="1" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg, Pennsylvania and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie, et est classé comme une propriété contributive.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is categorised as a contributing property and can be found in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est classé comme une propriété contributive et se trouve à Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument falls under the category of Contributing property and is placed in the municipality of Gettysburg in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi appartient à la catégorie des biens contributeurs et est situé dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="2" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the United States and falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e Mississippi Infantry Monument se trouve aux États-Unis et fait partie de la catégorie des biens contributifs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument falls under the category of Contributing property and is in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi appartient à la catégorie des biens contributifs et se trouve aux États-Unis.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, located in the United States, falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e Mississippi Infantry Monument, situé aux États-Unis, fait partie de la catégorie des biens contributeurs.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="3" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, established in 2000, is in the municipality of Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, créé en 2000, se trouve dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is placed in the municipality of Gettysburg in Pennsylvania and erected in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est érigé dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie, en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg Pennsylvania and was erected in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie, et a été érigé en 2000.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="4" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, situated in Adams County, Pennsylvania, is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, est classé comme une propriété contributive.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, et fait partie de la catégorie des biens contributifs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania and is categorised as a contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, et est classé comme une propriété contributive.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="5" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in 2000 and is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi a été créé en 2000 et est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument's location is Adams County, Pennsylvania and was established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, et a été établi en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Adams County, PA and was founded in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, et a été fondé en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in 2000 in Adams County, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi a été érigé en 2000 dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument in Adams County, Pennsylvania was established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, a été érigé en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id6" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument established in 2000 is found in Adams County, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id6" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, érigé en 2000, se trouve dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="6" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg, PA in Adams County.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie, dans le comté d'Adams.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in the municipality of Gettysburg, Adams County, in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve dans la municipalité de Gettysburg, dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The municipality for the 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is Gettysburg,Adams County, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">La municipalité où se trouve le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est Gettysburg, dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found in Adams County, Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve dans le comté d'Adams, à Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé dans le comté d'Adams, à Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="7" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | category | Contributing_property</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument falls under the category of Contributing property and is in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi appartient à la catégorie des biens contributifs et se trouve en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, which falls under the category of Contributing property, is in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, qui appartient à la catégorie des biens contributeurs, se trouve en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, in Pennsylvania, falls under the category of Contributing property.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, en Pennsylvanie, fait partie de la catégorie des biens contributifs.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="8" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | established | 2000</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found in Pennsylvania and was established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve en Pennsylvanie et a été créé en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, established in 2000 is in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument, fondée en 2000, se trouve en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument stands in the state of Pennsylvania and was established in 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est érigé dans l &quot;État de la Pennsylvanie et a été créé en 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in 2000 in Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument a été établi en 2000 en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument was established in Pennsylvania in the year 2000.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi a été érigé en Pennsylvanie en 2000.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="9" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Pennsylvania&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | municipality | Gettysburg,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry is found in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 11e régiment d'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve à Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is in Pennsylvania, in the municipality of Gettysburg.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi se trouve en Pennsylvanie, dans la municipalité de Gettysburg.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument can be found in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument can be found in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé à Gettysburg, en Pennsylvanie.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="10" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument, found in the Monocacy National Battlefield, is categorised as a historic district in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument, situé dans le champ de bataille national du Monocacy, est classé district historique aux États-Unis.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument belongs to the category of Historic districts in the United States and is found in the Monocacy National Battlefield.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument appartient à la catégorie des districts historiques aux États-Unis et se trouve dans le champ de bataille national du Monocacy.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is categorised as a historic district in the United States and is located in the Monocacy National Battlefield.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est classé district historique aux États-Unis et est situé dans le champ de bataille national du Monocacy.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="11" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument, which was established on July 11th 1907, belongs to the category of Historic districts in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument, créé le 11 juillet 1907, appartient à la catégorie des districts historiques aux États-Unis.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was founded on July 11, 1907 and belongs to the Historic districts of the U.S.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was founded on July 11, 1907 and belongs to the Historic districts of the U.S.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is categorised as a historic district in the United States and was established in 1907-07-11.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est classé district historique aux États-Unis et a été établi en 1907-07-11.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="12" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | category | Historic_districts_in_the_United_States</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument belongs to the category of Historic districts and is found in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument appartient à la catégorie des districts historiques et se trouve aux États-Unis.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the United States of America and is labelled as a historic district.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est situé aux États-Unis d'Amérique et est considéré comme un quartier historique.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument belongs to the category of Historic districts and is located in United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument appartient à la catégorie des districts historiques et se trouve aux États-Unis.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="13" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the United States at the Monocacy National Battlefield.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est situé aux États-Unis, sur le champ de bataille national du Monocacy.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the district of the Monocacy National Battlefield in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est situé dans le district du Monocacy National Battlefield aux États-Unis.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located in the Monocacy National Battlefield in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est situé dans le champ de bataille national du Monocacy, aux États-Unis.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="14" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | country | &quot;United States&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was made on July 11, 1907 and is located in the U.S.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was made on July 11, 1907 and is located in the U.S.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument was established on July 11th, 1907 and is in the United States.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument a été établi le 11 juillet 1907 aux États-Unis.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="15" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | district | Monocacy_National_Battlefield</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | established | &quot;1907-07-11&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is in the Monocacy National Battlefield and was founded July 11, 1907.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument se trouve dans le champ de bataille national du Monocacy et a été fondé le 11 juillet 1907.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is located on the Monocacy National Battlefield and was established on 11th July 1907.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument est situé sur le champ de bataille national du Monocacy et a été établi le 11 juillet 1907.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is in the Monocacy National Battlefield and was established July 11, 1907.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument se trouve sur le champ de bataille national du Monocacy et a été créé le 11 juillet 1907.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="16" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owner | National_Park_Service</otriple>
        <otriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Maryland&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | owner | National_Park_Service</mtriple>
        <mtriple>14th_New_Jersey_Volunteer_Infantry_Monument | state | &quot;Maryland&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monuments are in Maryland and are owned by the National Park Service.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Les 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monuments se trouvent au Maryland et appartiennent au National Park Service.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The National Park Service is the owner of the 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument and located in the state of Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le National Park Service est propriétaire du 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument et est situé dans l &quot;État du Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument is owned by the National Park Service and is in the state of Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le 14th New Jersey Volunteer Infantry Monument appartient au National Park Service et se trouve dans l &quot;État du Maryland.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="17" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | southeast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</otriple>
        <otriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | region | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Adams_County,_Pennsylvania | hasToItsSoutheast | Carroll_County,_Maryland</mtriple>
        <mtriple>11th_Mississippi_Infantry_Monument | location | Adams_County,_Pennsylvania</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Carroll County Maryland is southeast of Adams County Pennsylvania, where the 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Comté de Carroll Le Maryland est situé au sud-est du comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, où se trouve le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">To the southeast of Adams County , Pennsylvania where 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is found lies Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Au sud-est du comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, où se trouve le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, se trouve le comté de Carroll, au Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">To the southeast of Adams County, Pennsylvania, where11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located, lies Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Au sud-est du comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, où se trouve le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi, se trouve le comté de Carroll, au Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania which has Carroll County, Maryland to its southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania which has Carroll County, Maryland to its southeast.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">The 11th Mississippi Infantry Monument is located in Adams County, Pennsylvania, which is northwest of Carroll County, Maryland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Le 11e monument de l'infanterie du Mississippi est situé dans le comté d'Adams, en Pennsylvanie, au nord-ouest du comté de Carroll, au Maryland.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="18" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | open | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;^^xsd:date</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | inaugurationDate | &quot;1932-07-27&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The inauguration date for the Atatürk Monument (İzmir), made of bronze, is 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">La date d'inauguration du monument d'Atatürk (Izmir), en bronze, est 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The inauguration date of the Atatürk Monument, made of bronze, in Izmir is the 27th of July, 1932.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">La date d'inauguration du monument Atatürk, en bronze, à Izmir est le 27 Juillet, 1932.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Ataturk Monument (Izmir) was bronze and was inaugurated on 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le monument d'Ataturk (Izmir) était en bronze et a été inauguré le 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">The Atatürk Monument (made of bronze) in Izmir was inaugurated on 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">Le monument Atatürk (en bronze) à Izmir a été inauguré le 1932-07-27.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">The inauguration date of the bronze Ataturk Monument was July 27th, 1932.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Le monument de bronze Ataturk a été inauguré le 27 juillet 1932.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="19" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | material | &quot;Bronze&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Atatürk_Monument_(İzmir) | designer | Pietro_Canonica</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Pietro Canonica is the designer of the Ataturk Monument in Izmir, which is made of bronze.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Pietro Canonica est le concepteur du monument Ataturk à Izmir, qui est fait de bronze.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Atatürk Monument in Izmir, made of bronze, was designed by Pietro Canonica.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le monument Atatürk à Izmir, en bronze, a été conçu par Pietro Canonica.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Ataturk Monument designed by Pietro Canonica is made of Bronze.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le monument Ataturk conçu par Pietro Canonica est en bronze.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="20" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | capital | Baku</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is located in Baku, the capital of Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le mémorial des martyrs turcs est situé à Bakou, capitale de l'Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is in Azerbaijan. The capital is Baku.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Bakou Le mémorial des martyrs turcs se trouve en Azerbaïdjan, la capitale étant Bakou.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Turkish martyrs memorial is located in Baku, the capital of Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le mémorial des martyrs turcs se trouve à Bakou, capitale de l'Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="21" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | leaderTitle | Prime_Minister_of_Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The leader of Azerbaijan is called the Prime Minister. The Baku Turkish Martyr's Memorial is in Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le chef de l'Azerbaïdjan s'appelle le Premier ministre et le monument commémoratif des martyrs turcs de Bakou se trouve en Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is located in Azerbaijan and the leader is The Prime Minister of Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Bakou Le mémorial des martyrs turcs se trouve en Azerbaïdjan et son chef est le Premier Ministre d'Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">Azerbaijan's leader is the Prime Minister. The Baku Turkish Martyr's Memorial is in Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le chef de file de l'Azerbaïdjan est le Premier ministre et le monument commémoratif des martyrs turcs de Bakou se trouve en Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="22" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner created the Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial. It is made of red granite and white marble.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Huseyin Butuner et Hilmi Guner ont créé le Mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou, fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The designers of the Red granite and white marble Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial are Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Les créateurs du Mémorial des Martyrs turcs de Bakou sont Hüseyin Bütüner et Hilmi Güner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is designed by Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner and is made with red granite and white marble.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le monument commémoratif des martyrs turcs de Bakou a été conçu par Huseyin Butuner et Hilmi Guner et est fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyr's Memorial, designed by Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner, is made out of red granite and white marble.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id4" lang="fr">Le monument commémoratif des martyrs turcs de Bakou, conçu par Hüseyin Bütüner et Hilmi Güner, est fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="en">Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner designed the Baku Turkish Martyrs' Monument which is made of red granite and white marble.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id5" lang="fr">Huseyin Butuner et Hilmi Guner ont conçu le monument des martyrs turcs de Bakou, fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="23" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Azerbaijan | legislature | National_Assembly_(Azerbaijan)</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Azerbaijan | legislature | National_Assembly_(Azerbaijan)</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The National Assembly dictates the legislature of Azerbaijan, where the Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is found.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">L'Assemblée nationale dicte le choix de l'organe législatif de l'Azerbaïdjan, où se trouve le mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The National Assembly (Azerbaijan) is the source of legislature in Azerbaijan, where the Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is located.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">L'Assemblée nationale (Azerbaïdjan) est la source du pouvoir législatif en Azerbaïdjan, où se trouve le mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="24" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | location | Azerbaijan</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | material | &quot;Red granite and white marble&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial made of red granite and white marble can be found in Azerbaijan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou, fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc, se trouve en Azerbaïdjan.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is located in Azerbaijan and made of red granite and white marble.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou est situé en Azerbaïdjan et est fait de granit rouge et de marbre blanc.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="25" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;@en</otriple>
        <otriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;@en</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | nativeName | &quot;Türk Şehitleri Anıtı&quot;</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Baku_Turkish_Martyrs'_Memorial | designer | &quot;Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner&quot;</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The native name for the Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial, designed by Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner is Türk Şehitleri Anıtı.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Le nom d'origine du mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou, conçu par Hüseyin Bütüner et Hilmi Güner, est Türk Şehitleri Anıtı.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs'Memorial which is know locally as Turk Sehitleri Anti was designed by Huseyin Butuner and Hilmi Guner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">Le monument commémoratif des martyrs turcs de Bakou, connu localement sous le nom de Turk Sehitleri Anti, a été conçu par Huseyin Butuner et Hilmi Guner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Baku Turkish Martyrs' Memorial is known in Turkish as Turk Sehitleri Aniti and the designers are Hüseyin Bütüner and Hilmi Güner.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">Le mémorial des martyrs turcs de Bakou est connu en turc sous le nom de Turk Sehitleri Aniti et les créateurs sont Hüseyin Bütüner et Hilmi Güner.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="26" size="2" shape="(X (X) (X))" shape_type="sibling">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | material | Rock_(geology)</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is made from rock and is in ENgland.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">The Dead Man's Plack est fait de roche et se trouve en ENgland.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="27" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | capital | London</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | capital | London</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is located in England, the capital of which is London.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">The Dead Man's Plack est situé en Angleterre, dont la capitale est Londres.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is in London, England.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">The Dead Man's Plack se trouve à Londres, en Angleterre.</lex>
    </entry>
    <entry category="Monument" eid="28" size="2" shape="(X (X (X)))" shape_type="chain">
      <originaltripleset>
        <otriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</otriple>
        <otriple>England | ethnicGroups | British_Arabs</otriple>
      </originaltripleset>
      <modifiedtripleset>
        <mtriple>Dead_Man's_Plack | location | England</mtriple>
        <mtriple>England | ethnicGroup | British_Arabs</mtriple>
      </modifiedtripleset>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="en">Dead Man's Plack is in England and one of the ethnic groups found in England is the British Arabs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id1" lang="fr">Dead Man's Plack est en Angleterre et l'un des groupes ethniques que l'on trouve en Angleterre est celui des Arabes britanniques.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is in England honoring the British Arab ethnic group.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id2" lang="fr">The Dead Man's Plack est en Angleterre en hommage au groupe ethnique arabe britannique.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="en">The Dead Man's Plack is located in England, where one of the ethnic groups is the British Arabs.</lex>
      <lex comment="" lid="Id3" lang="fr">The Dead Man's Plack est situé en Angleterre, où l'un des groupes ethniques est celui des Arabes britanniques.</lex>
    </entry>
  </entries>
</benchmark>
